# Jeremiah Wodke

## **Full-Stack Software Engineer with Graphic Design Experience**

(970) 391-2132 - Jeremiah.wodke@gmail.com

Experienced Web Developer with a demonstrated history of working with various technologies and platforms. Skilled in PHP, JavaScript, and modern frontend technologies. Experience building custom PHP applications, WordPress, WooCommerce, Shopify, BigCommerce and Web Project Management. My dream job consists of working with a small group of artisans who believe in beautiful code, ridiculous humor and that their software can help make our world a better place.

To view some of my personal projects please visit my portfolio website

# http://jeremiahwodke.com

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### **MadWire Media**, Fort Collins, CO — R&D Software Engineer

May 1st, 2018 - Present

As a Research and Development Software Developer at MadWire Media I have the privilege of creating and improving the software that automates and improves the internal workflows of our talented marketing team, SEO experts, web developers, consultants and more.

## MadWire Media, Fort Collins, CO — Custom Web Developer

May 1st, 2017 - Present

In my custom web developer position I create custom themes for Wordpress / WooCommerce, Shopify, and BigCommerce. I've also created custom PHP applications utilizing MVC and OOP paradigms.

### **Peak Studios**, Remote/Boulder, CO — Web Developer

July 15th, 2015 - July 15th 2016

Assisting in the creation and/or maintainability of Wordpress templates for companies including but not limited to Chem-Dry, Marco's Pizza, Brand Journalists, N-Hance Wood Renewal and more.

## **Peak Studios,** Remote/Boulder, CO — *Director of SEO*

Jan 1st, 2013 - July 15th 2016

I ran a small team whose tasks were to methodically analyze and increase the paid and organic SEO for numerous corporate franchises. Corporations include; Chem-Dry and N-Hance Revolutionary Wood Renewal. Being that Peak Studios is a small consultancy I had to fill a lot of positions to meet the demands of our clients. I truly enjoyed working with our clients and watching our marketing strategy help their businesses grow.

#### Web Development

PHP, OOP, MVC, Yii, Guzzle,
Docker, Large System
Architecture, MySQL, HTML5,
CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery,
Handlebars.js, Vue.js, SASS,
Bootstrap 3, Grunt, Wordpress,
WooCommerce, Wordpress Plugin
Development, NPM, Version
Control (Git), Liquid (Shopify),
Jekyll, UX Design Principles,
REST Apis, AJAX, CRUD,
Cross-Browser Testing,
Responsive Web Design

#### **Graphic Design**

High-Fidelity Mock-Ups, Photoshop, Asset Restoration, Asset Optimization, Professional Photograph, (Basic) Adobe Illustrator CS6

#### **REFERENCES**

James Vucinovich
President / Client
Rossi Vucinovich PC Law Firm
(425) 646-8003 |
jvucinovich@rvflegal.com

Quince Wyss CEO Peak Studios (303) 819-3968 | quince@peakstudios.com

Sam Ringleman Web Developer at MadWire (970) 460-4255 | sam@impactstud.io

#### **EDUCATION**

## Front Range Community College, Fort Collins, CO

2010 - 2012 (Some College)

→ Associates of Arts

## Udacity, Online

2016

→ Frontend Developer Nanodegree

## Flatiron School, Online

2016

- → JavaScript Basics
- → JavaScript Section of Full Stack Developer Program

## Launch School, Online

2016

- **Programming Fundamentals**
- HTML and CSS

## **Udemy Online Learning**

2016

- → Wordpress Theme Development with Bootstrap
   → The Complete Wordpress Developer Course
   → PHP for Beginners: Become a PHP Master
   → Photoshop for Web Design
   → Object Oriented Programming in PHP